face2faceafrica.com 2015-03-23

# Privacy Statement | Face2FaceAfrica

30January 2014

Face2FaceAfrica

## Privacy Statement

Face2Face Africa, LLC., and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, "F2FA"), respects the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognizes the importance of protecting all information that you may choose to share with us.  To further this commitment, we have adopted this Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to guide how we collect, store and use the information you provide to us.

  1. **_Information Covered_**

This Privacy Policy applies only to personal information collected on the websites where this Privacy Policy is posted (http://www.face2faceafrica.com, http://www.Facelistawards.com and http://www.f2famagazine.com).

This Privacy Policy applies to the use and sharing of personal information collected on and after the date that this Privacy Policy is posted.

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted and collected online, and does not apply to information that may be collected by Face2Face Africa, LLC. offline.  This Privacy Policy applies only to websites maintained by F2FA, and not to our international affiliates, or any websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link.  F2FA, therefore, is not responsible for the content or activities provided on those websites.

Finally, the terms of this Privacy Policy are subject to all applicable United States laws.

**           2.   _Information Collected_**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.  However, we do not require personal information to access our websites and you may visit our websites anonymously.  In the event that you prefer not to disclose personal information, please keep in mind that you may not be able to enjoy certain features of our websites.  Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you.  To offer our guests certain features on our websites, we may collect several types of personally identifiable information.  Personal information that you provide to us can be attained via various means:

  * Information You Provide to Us:  The majority of the personal information we receive comes directly from our guests.  This information may include: Name, E-mail Address, and/or Telephone Number.  We may collect personal information from our guests to:

**                              i. **Participate in contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions;

                             **ii.** Report piracy, offer feedback, or other business inquiries; and/or  
                     **         iii. **Sign up to receive newsletters.

  * Information Collected Through Technology:  We collect information through technology to make our websites more interesting and useful to you.  For example, when you come to one of our websites, we collect your IP address.  An IP address often is associated with the portal through which you enter the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company or your university.  Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable.  At times, we also use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our websites.  We do not combine the information collected through technology with your personally identifiable information.

  * Cookies: Our websites also use cookies.  Cookies are pieces of information that a website sends to your computer while you are viewing the website.  We and other companies use cookies for a variety of purposes.  For example, when you return to one of our websites after logging in, cookies provide information to the website so that the website will remember who you are.  You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies.  You can do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings.  Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your web experience smoother, like the features mentioned above, and some of our services may not function properly.

**                    3\. _Use of Personal Information_**

We do not share, sell or rent your personal information to third parties without your consent.  We do not require disclosure of personal information to access our websites as our websites can be accessed anonymously.  However, if you prefer not to disclose any personal information, you may not be able to enjoy certain features of our website.

We will only collect information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives, such as:

  1. To personalize your experience:  Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.  Information collected from those who voluntarily submit it to us is used to provide services like updates on special events and e-mail announcements of interest to our users. We do not share your personally identifiable information with third party marketers.   
  2. To send periodic emails:  The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates, including but not limited to, receiving occasional company news, updates, or administrative communications either about your account with us or about features of our websites, including any future changes to this Privacy Policy.  NOTE: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, F2FA includes detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
  3. To improve our customer service and our websites:  We occasionally use third parties (other companies, agents or contractors) to perform services necessary to our operations.  For example, we have partnered with other companies to personalize our web pages, analyze customers' interaction with our website, send newsletters and process consumer surveys.  In the course of providing such services, these private, third party companies may have contact with your personally identifiable information and have agreed to securely store and maintain the personal information received from us and only use your personally identifiable information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
  4. To help protect the security and safety of Our websites and others:  We will disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that such disclosures (a) are required by law, including, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena, or (b) will help to: enforce our terms of use; enforce contests, sweepstakes, promotions; protect your safety or security, including the safety and security of property that belongs to you; and/or protect the safety and security of our websites or third parties.

           **        4\. _Protection of Personal Information_**

The security and confidentiality of your information is extremely important to us.  We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and improper use.  We use industry standard practices such as physically secured rooms and password protection systems to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information.  From time to time, we review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods.  However, please understand that, despite our best efforts, no security measure is perfect or impenetrable.

          **      5\. _Third Party Links_**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our websites.  These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies.  For instance, clicking on an advertisement or on links or other elements on the website may take you to an entirely different website.  Links to other sites may use our website logo or style as a result of a co-branding agreement.  These websites may send their own cookies to you and may collect data and make use of that data in ways that this website would not.  Once you have left this website, this Privacy Policy will no longer apply to personally identifiable information or any other data collected from or provided by you.  Please check the applicable privacy policy to determine how that website will handle such data.

We therefore have **NO** responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites.  Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our websites and welcome any feedback about these third party sites.

**              6\. _Disclosure of Information to Outside Parties_**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside third parties your personally identifiable information.  This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our websites, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  We further reserve the right to share personally identifiable information with our affiliates for their marketing purposes.  However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

         **         7\. _Message Boards, Chat Rooms, Blogs and Other User Forums_**

Please remember that information posted to message boards, chat rooms, blogs and other user forums becomes public information.  Use caution when posting.  Individuals under the age of 18 should be especially careful not to provide any personally identifiable information when participating in any area of the website where postings might become public.

**                   8\. _Children and Privacy_**

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be fully familiar with the websites visited by their children.  Children under the age of thirteen (13) years of age are expressly prohibited from submitting or posting any personally identifiable information on the website or other services.

                   **9. _Your Consent_**

By using our websites, you accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

**                    10\. _Amendments and Changes to Our Privacy Policy_**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time.  Any changes made will be conducted by prominently posting notice of the changes on this webpage.  Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective 30 days following our posting of notice of the changes on the websites covered by this Privacy Policy.

This policy was last modified on March 5th, 2012.

**                   11\. _Contacting Us_**

How can you ask questions, or send us comments, about this Privacy Policy?

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please send us an e-mail with your questions or comments or call or write us at:

**Face2Face Africa, LLC.  
info@f2fafrica.com  
888.505.1299**

Please be assured that any personal information that you provide in communications to the above e-mail will not be used to send you promotional materials, unless you request it.
